Finding Aid for the Renée Levine Packer Papers, 1963-circa 2015
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Renée Levine Packer Papers, 1963-circa 2015
Mus. Arc. 75
Levine Packer, Renée, 1940-
28 boxes (636 folders/items)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
The collection consists of personal and research papers belonging to Renée Levine Packer, including correspondence and files for her books: This life of sounds and Gay Guerrilla. It also includes recordings of interviews conducted by Levine-Packer for her book research as well as inscribed books and commercial recordings.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Renée Levine Packer, August 2015.
Accruals and Additions
Additional materials related to research on Julius Eastman for the book, Gay Guerrilla are expected to be sent.
Biographical Note
Renée Levine Packer (née Wennerholm) was born in Nice, France and raised in New York and Mexico City. After working at the Dance Department at The Juilliard School and at the national headquarters of Young Audiences, Inc., Levine Packer moved to Buffalo, New York in 1964 after her husband, Jesse Levine, attained the position of principal viola with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra for the 1964-1965 season. Lukas Foss and Allen Sapp created the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts at the State University of New York at Buffalo using funds from the Rockefeller Foundation. The first year of operation was 1964 and the Center was soon in need of a coordinator and manager to handle all the details concerning the fellows of the Center, known as Creative Associates, as well as all the logistics involved with producing concerts in Buffalo, New York City, and elsewhere. Levine Packer was hired in January 1965 as an assistant to Richard Wernick. When Wernick left in spring of 1965, Levine Packer was hired as Center Coordinator. She served in that title until 1974 when she also became the Center's Managing Director until her departure in 1978.
Levine Packer left the University at Buffalo in 1978 to go to the California Institute of the Arts (Cal Arts) to serve as Director of Admissions and Records until 1982. While at Cal Arts Renée also served as Director of Contemporary Music Festival. Following her work at Cal Arts, Levine Packer moved to Washington, D.C. to work as the Director of the Inter-Arts Program at the National Endowment for the Arts 1982-1986. from 1986-1993, Levine Packer worked as an independent arts consultant and producer. In this role she was responsible for a production of Robert Longo's theater work, Killing Angels in 1987 at Buffalo State College and a production of Steve Reich and Beryl Korot's video-opera The Cave in 1993. She also conducted a national survey on alternative arts organizations in the United States for the Ford Foundation and conducted a survey and wrote a report for Georgetown University concerning the creation of a performing arts center and program of public performances. Levine Packer served as Dean of Continuing Studies at the Maryland Institute, College of Art 1992-2000.
Renée Levine Packer's educational background includes earning a B.A. degree in arts administration from the State University of New York Empire State College and attendance at the Harvard Institute of Arts Administration in 1973. She earned a Master of Liberal Arts degree from Johns Hopkins University in 2001. She began her research on the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts as part of her studies at Johns Hopkins, writing her thesis, In the Center: The Center of the Creative and Performing Arts in the State University of New York at Buffalo, as her thesis. The thesis then served as the basis for her Oxford University Press book, This Life of Sounds: Evenings for New Music in Buffalo (2010). Levine Packer's next book project was Gay Guerrilla: Julius Eastman and His Music (University of Rochester Press, 2015), which she conceived and for which she served as co-editor with Mary Jane Leach and contributor of the major biographical chapter.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains the papers of author and arts administrator Renée Levine Packer. It includes a small number of personal documents, such as résumés, and personal correspondence. The majority of the content was created in the process of writing This Life of Sounds: Evenings for New Music in Buffalo, and writing and editing Gay Guerrilla: Julius Eastman and His Music. Also included are working files for Levine-Packer's rôle as producer of performances of Robert Longo's Killing Angels and Steve Reich and Beryl Korot's The Cave. Additional content includes clippings, programs, photographs, cassette recordings of interviews for both books, signed books and recordings.
There is considerable overlap within the collection. For example, composer John Cage is represented as a subject, a correspondent, as an author and composer, and by a series of folders of contents collected by Levine Packer for other purposes. The collection was chiefly received within folders with titles by the creator. The contents of the folders were maintained and titles were kept wherever feasible. Dates for folder contents are supplied where easily discerned.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in twelve series:
I. Personal documents and writings
II. Book, interview, and research files for This Life of Sounds
III. Production files for Robert Longo's Killing Angels
IV. Production files for Steve Reich and Beryl Korot's The Cave
V. John Cage files
VI. Correspondence
VII. Books with inscriptions
VIII. Programs and journal issues
IX. Photographs
X. Scores
XI. Sound recordings
XII. Book, interview, and research files for Gay Guerrilla: Julius Eastman and His Music
Container List
- Personal documents and writings, 1975-1999, I.; Folder 1-17
  Arranged in two subseries:
  A. Personal documents
  B. Writings
  - Personal documents, undated, I.A; Folder 1-3
    Contains small number of self-written biographical sketches, résumés, and clippings about Levine Packer.
    - Biographies, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 001)
    - Resumes, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 002)
    - Personal clippings, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 003)
  - Writings, 1975-1999, I.B; Folder 4-17
    Contains some of Renée Levine Packer's writings, included unpublished texts. Dates are supplied when known.
    Alphabetically arranged by title.
    - Buffalo panel, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 005)
    - City: past, present and future: Buffalo: Queen City of the lakes, 1999, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 006)
    - Dance: the arts in collaboration, 1986, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 007)
    - John Cage introduction, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 008)
    - Maverick in American music, 1998, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 009)
    - National Endowment for the Arts: 20th anniversary talk, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 010)
      On note cards.
    - National Endowment for the Arts: Interview with Renee Levine, 1982, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 011)
      In National Endowment for the Arts' The cultural Post
    - New Music America: program introduction, 1983, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 012)
    - Proposal for MLA graduate project, 1999, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 013)
    - Speech for Cal State Long Beach: Inter Arts, 1987, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 014)
    - Thoughts on the Center, 1975, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 015)
    - Three voices (1982) by Morton Feldman, 1988, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 016)
    - Untitled writings and Resignation letter, Maryland Institute, College of Art, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 017)
- Book, interview, and research files for This Life of Sounds 1963-2011, II.; Folder 18-380
  Contains all the files and interview recordings associated with the book, This Life of Sounds and the master's thesis on which it was based, In the Center: The Center of the Creative and Performing Arts in the State University of New York at Buffalo. There is no attempt at separation of the documentation concerning the thesis versus the published book since many of the files were used for both.
  Arranged into seven subseries:
  A. Book content files
  B. Book business files
  C. Interview transcriptions and correspondence
  D. Subject files
  E. Supplementary University at Buffalo Music Library Catalogs and University at Buffalo publications about student unrest
  F. Interview recordings
  G. Electronic files for book and interview transcriptions
  - Book content files, circa 2000-2010, II.A; Folder 18-32
    This subseries contains folders related to the genesis of the text.
    Alphabetically arranged by folder title.
    - Addresses and contacts, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 018)
    - Book content: Appendices, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 019)
    - Book content: Bibliography, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 020)
    - Book content: Contents, timeline, bibliography, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 021)
    - Book content: Drafts, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 022)
    - Book content: End notes, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 023)
    - Book content: Final section notes, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 024)
    - Book content: Outlines and beginnings, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 025)
    - Book content: Postscript, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 026)
    - Book content: Resources, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 027)
    - Book content: Thesis notes, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 028)
    - Book content: Timeline, 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 029)
    - Photographs (photocopies), 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 030-031)
    - Photographs (photocopies): Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 032)
  - Book business files, 2000-2011, II.B; Folder 33-43
    Content related to the publication and marketing of the book, as well as expenses, permissions, and comments from peer review readers.
    - ASCAP Deems Taylor Award, 2011, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 033)
    - Correspondence: Childress, Lucy, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 034)
    - Correspondence: Locke, Ralph, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 035)
      For University of Rochester Press
    - Correspondence: Oxford University Press, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 036)
    - Correspondence: State University of New York Press, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 037)
    - Correspondence: University of Rochester Press, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 038)
    - Expenses, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 039)
    - Marketing, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 040)
    - Permissions: Poons, Larry, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 041)
    - Permissions: Texts, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 042)
    - Readers' notes and reviews, 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 043)
  - Interview transcriptions and correspondence, circa 1999-2001, II.C; Folder 44-98
    The interviews were originally conducted for the thesis version of the text where the transcriptions were included as an appendix. The folders in some cases include correspondence and printouts of email. Some interviewees were only contacted via email rather than recorded in person.
    Alphabetically arranged by interviewee surname, with lists at the beginning.
    - Interviewee lists, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 044)
    - Interviews notebook, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 045)
    - Amacher, Maryanne, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 046)
    - Anthone, Alyssa Rabach, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 047)
    - Baca, Carlotta, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 048)
    - Bannon, Anthony, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 049)
    - Bergamo, John, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 050)
    - Berlow, Sheldon, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 051)
    - Blum, Eberhard, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 052)
    - Brigham-Dimiziani, Sylvia, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 053)
    - Brown, Earle, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 054)
    - Buck, Robert, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 055)
    - Chadabe, Joel, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 056)
    - Crumb, George, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 057)
    - Di Pietro, Rocco, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 058)
    - Felder, David, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 059)
    - Feldman, Barbara Monk, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 060)
    - Foss Lukas, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 061)
    - Fox, Stuart, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 062)
    - Fulkerson, James, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 063)
    - Fuller, David, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 064)
    - Gena, Peter, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 065)
    - Globokar, Vinko, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 066)
    - Harriott, Esther, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 067)
    - Hassell, Jon, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 068)
    - Hornbacher, Sara, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 069)
    - Haupt, Charles, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 070)
    - Kahle, Dennis, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 071)
    - Kotík, Petr, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 072)
    - Kubera, Joseph, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 073)
    - Lawson, Christyne, 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 074)
    - Levine, George, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 075)
    - Levine-Packer, Renée, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 076)
      Interviewed by John Spitzer.
    - Martin, Robert, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 077)
    - Mischel, Howard, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 078)
    - Moog, Robert, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 079)
    - O'Grady, Gerald, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 080)
    - Plantamura, Carol, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 081)
    - Pousseur, Henri, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 082)
    - Rosenboom, David, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 083)
    - Rzewski, Frederic, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 084)
    - Sahl, Michael, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 085)
    - Schneider, June, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 086)
    - Shostac, David, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 087)
    - Siemering, William, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 088)
    - Sollberger, Harvey, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 089)
    - Stiller, Andrew, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 090)
    - Verberne, Marijke, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 091)
    - Vigeland, Nils, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 092)
    - Warren, Gwendolin Sims, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 093)
    - Wernick, Richard, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 094)
    - Williams, Diane, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 095)
    - Williams, Jan, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 096)
    - Wrochem, Klaus von, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 097)
    - Yadzinski, Edward, 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 098)
  - Subject files, circa 1999-2010, II.D; Folder 99-267
    Contains the subject research files for the book. Note that folders for personal names may contain correspondence, material treating the person as a subject, or articles by the person. The range of dates represents when the material was collected, not the date of the original documents. There are 24 folders related to the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts and another 13 folders of clippings about Center events. The Rockefeller Foundation was the original source of funding for the Center and is represented by 11 folders of content. For the most part, folder content has been maintained as received.
    - Almquist, Sharon G., 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 099)
    - Amacher, Maryanne, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - American Society of University Composers Newsletter, 1968, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Art history context, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Artpark, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Arts support in the United States, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Attica Correctional Facility, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Babbitt, Milton, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Bard College, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Béhague, Gerard, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 108)
      His article, Popular music
    - Bewley, John, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Blum, Eberhard, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Boretz, Benjamin, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Brown, Earle, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Buck, Robert, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 113)
      Albright-Knox Art Gallery.
    - Buffalo and Erie County Public Library, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Buffalo: Architecture and more, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Buffalo: bibliographic references, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Buffalo: Blizzard, 1977, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Buffalo Evening News, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Buffalo Festival of the Arts, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Cage, John, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Cardew, Cornelius, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Carnegie Hall/National Public Radio, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Carter, Elliott, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Renée Levine job correspondence, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Renée Levine job description, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Administration, 1974, 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Concert lists, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Creative Associates addresses and correspondence, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Creative Associates community involvement, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Creative Associates complaint letter, 1965-03-05, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: European tours, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Finances - Budget, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Finances - Fiscal condition, 1970-1971, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Finances - Fiscal summary, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 134)
      With content by Lejaren Hiller.
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Finances - Funding issues, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 135)
      With content by Allen Sapp.
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: History, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 136)
      With content by Carol June Bradley and Edward Yadzinski.
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: History - Birtwistle concert disagreement, 1975, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 137)
      With content by Morton Feldman and Jan Williams.
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: History - Demise, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: History - Scenario, 1973, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 139)
      Paper by Renée Levine-Packer.
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: History - Scenario part 2, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 140)
      With content by Renée Levine-Packer and Allen Sapp.
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: History - Summary report by Renée Levine, 1977, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Letterhead and brochures, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Objectives, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Recordings, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Regionalization, 1972, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Reorganization, 1976, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 146)
      With content by Jan Williams and Renée Levine-Packer.
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Rosters of Creative Associates, 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Clippings, 1964-1966, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Clippings, 1967-1969, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Clippings, 1970-1980, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Clippings - Buffalo press, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Creative Associate Recitals clippings and programs, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Clippings - Evenings for New Music, 1973, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Evenings for New Music program notes, 1971-1980, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Evenings for New Music program card, 1977-05-07, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Evenings for New Music programs, 1965-1977, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Flyers, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Program for performance at The Kitchen, 1977-03-23, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Catalog of Creative Associate Recitals, 1964-1980, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Center of the Creative and Performing Arts: Catalog of Evenings for New Music programs, 1964-1977, 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - CEPA Gallery, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Cohen, Albert, 1970-1971, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 162)
      On Center's influence on Music Department.
    - Contemporary Chamber Ensemble, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 163)
      And its founder Arthur Weisberg.
    - Crumb, George, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Del Tredici, David, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - Dufallo, Richard, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - Dunn, Joseph, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - Dylan, Bob, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - Electric Circus (Nightclub), 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 169)
    - Electricity, 1984, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 170)
      Article by K. C. Cole.
    - Electronic music, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 171)
    - Experiments in Art and Technology (EAT), 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 172)
    - Feldman, Morton, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 173)
    - Feldman, Morton - Clippings, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 174)
    - Feldman, Morton - Neither, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 175)
    - Fluxus, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 176)
    - Foss, Lukas, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 177)
    - Getty Research Institute. Research Library, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 178)
    - Hentoff, Nat, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 179)
    - Gitlin, Todd, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 180)
    - Green, Alan, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 181)
      Excerpts from thesis on Allen Sapp.
    - Hallwalls (Museum), 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 182)
    - Harrison, Lou, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 183)
    - Hiller, Lejaren, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 184)
      With information about Lejaren Hiller, Sr.
    - Hiller, Lejaren - HPSCHD, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 185)
    - Horowitz, Joseph, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 186)
    - IRCAM, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 187)
    - Jackson, Bruce, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 188)
      With lyrics of Hayes Hall Blues.
    - Jolas, Betsy, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 189)
    - June in Buffalo (Festival; 1975-1980), 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 190)
    - June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 191)
    - Kagel, Mauricio, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 192)
    - Knox, Seymour, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 193)
      With proposal for a history of the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts.
    - Kondo, Jo, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 194)
    - Kotík, Petr, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 195)
    - Kvistad, Garry, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 196)
    - La Barbara, Joan, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 197)
    - Larrabee, Eric, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 198)
    - Léandre, Joélle, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 199)
    - Lennon, John, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 200)
    - Lucier, Alvin, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 201)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Center for Advanced Visual Studies, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 202)
    - Mathews, Max, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 203)
    - Metz, Donald, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 204)
    - Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 205)
    - Minimalism, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 206)
    - Moog, Robert, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 207)
    - Mumma, Gordon, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 208)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - proposals, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 209)
    - Neuhaus, Max, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 210)
    - New York City Blackout of 1965, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 211)
    - North American New Music Festival, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 212)
    - O'Grady, Gerald, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 213)